[
  {
    "front": "responder",
    "back": "antwoorden",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "ameaÃ§a",
    "back": "bedreiging",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.802Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "importante",
    "back": "belangrijk",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "em breve, logo",
    "back": "binnenkort",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "ElÃ©trico, movido a eletricidade (âš¡)",
    "back": "elektrisch",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Perigoso (â˜ ï¸)",
    "back": "gevaarlijk",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "PrisÃ£o (ğŸ›ï¸)",
    "back": "gevangenis",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "AvÃ´ (ğŸ‘´)",
    "back": "grootvader",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Lembrar-se (ğŸ§ )",
    "back": "herinneren",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Instrumento, ferramenta (ğŸ»)",
    "back": "instrument",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Naturalmente (ğŸŒ±)",
    "back": "natuurlijk",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Escapar (ğŸƒâ€â™‚ï¸ğŸ’¨)",
    "back": "ontsnappen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Assaltar, invadir (ğŸƒâ€â™‚ï¸ğŸ’¥)",
    "back": "overvallen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Restaurante (ğŸ½ï¸)",
    "back": "restaurant",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Gritar (ğŸ—£ï¸)",
    "back": "schreeuwen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Quarto (ğŸ›ï¸)",
    "back": "slaapkamer",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Retorno, volta (ğŸ”„)",
    "back": "terugkomst",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Convidar (âœ‰ï¸ğŸ‰)",
    "back": "uitnodigen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Mudar, alterar (ğŸ”„)",
    "back": "veranderen",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Triste, sofrido (ğŸ˜¢)",
    "back": "verdrietig",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  }
]